### Mochammad Alif Pratama

### Senior IT Support Assistant

o Address Bogor, Indonesia

E-mail alifpratamaaa99@gmail.com

o Phone +6289663084201

LinkedIn Mochammad Alif Pratama

I have experience in IT support for approximately 4 years. Hardworking and passionate job seekers with always learning skills in the IT field and strong organizational skills want to get the best IT positions, like specialists and experts. Ready to assist the team in achieving company goals.

# Work Experience

#### Senior IT Support Assistant • PT. Vivo Mobile Indonesia

- · Identified issues, analyzed information, and provided solutions to problems
- · Asset management for all IT devices.
- · Learned and adapted quickly to new technology and software applications
- Communicated with IT from HQ

May 2022 - Now

#### IT SupportAssistant • PT. Vivo Mobile Indonesia

- Performhardware, software, and network troubleshooting
- Ensure the network is stable and well-functioning.
- · Asset management for all IT devices
- · Maintenance of computers, servers, CCTV, and printers
- Support IT project from HQ

Sept 2020 - May 2022

#### Office Boy • PT. Vivo Mobile Indonesia

- · Ensuring the room is neat and clean
- · washing eating and drinking utensils.
- · Keeping records of inventory of office goods and IT equipment
- · Performhardware and software troubleshooting.
- · Computer network support
- · Ensure that peripheral devices work properly.
- · Deliver foreign documents to immigration, the Department of Manpower, and Disdukcapil
- Accompany foreigners to take photos at immigration to immigration.

Jul 2017 - Sept 2020

# Education



Oct 2018 - August 2022

### STMIK Jayakarta

Bachelor of Technology

# Certifications

- · CCNA: Introduction to Networks
- CCNA: Switching, Routing, and Wireless Essentials
- CCNA: Enterprise Networking, Security, and Automation
- IT Support Google specialization.
- AWS Academy Graduate AWS Academy Cloud Foundations

### Skills

- Troubleshooting
- Networking
- Linux Administration
- Routing
- Cloud Foundations
- Fundamental Programming

# **Project**

- Create an Asset management system based on the local server.
- Create a ticketing system and internal articles based on the local server.